Guide to the Albert Waldo Snoke Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Oversize
  - Personal and Family Papers
    - Snoke, Albert: awards and certificates, 1933-1979 (Box 55, Folder 2-3)
  - Photographs
    - Chronological, n.d. (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - Groups: Yale University. School of Nursing deans, ca., 1950 (Box 55, Folder 5)